using
a built-in hash method we're going to
write a program that loops through this
hash
and prints all of the keys
we can see that our hash here opposites
has three key value pairs
looking at the hash documentation we see
a method
each key so this looks like a good
candidate for what we're trying to do
we'll call this method on the hash
and each key is going to be passed to
the block as an argument
and we simply want to output each key
we'll invoke put us
and now when we run our code we should
see each of these three keys
output on its own line
and that's what we see
so moving on to the next part of our
problem
we need to write a program that does the
same thing here except
prints the values again
looking back at the hash documentation
we conveniently have a method that can
help us do this
each value will iterate through
each value of the calling hash
so let's name our block parameter
appropriately
and again we'll use put s to output the
value
now lastly we want to write a program
that prints both the key and value
so instead of calling each key or each
value
we can simply call the each method
each will iterate through our hash and
pass both the key
and value as arguments to the block
so we'll name our block parameters
accordingly
and then output a message with both the
key and value
and we'll use string interpolation here
now when we run our code we'll see our
display message which will include both
the key and
value
and that's what we see